<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<listings>
  <event id="63676">
    <headline_as_text>San Francisco Ballet's "Nutcracker", Set in the City by the Bay</headline_as_text>
    <sold_out>false</sold_out>
    <image>https://i.goldstar.com/gse_media/112/11/sfballet-nutcracker-120312.jpg</image>
    <summary_as_html>On Christmas Eve 1944, &lt;em&gt;Nutcracker&lt;/em&gt; made its American debut in San Francisco. So it's only fitting that when San Francisco Ballet Artistic Director and Principal Choreographer Helgi Tomasson set out to stage a new production of the beloved family favorite more than 60 years later, he chose the City by the Bay as the backdrop. Set in San Francisco during the 1915 World's Fair, Clara's dreamlike journey is an ode to the city's historical grandeur -- set amidst colorful, larger-than-life scenery, more than 200 dazzling costumed characters, and of course Tchaikovsky's beautiful score performed live by the world-class San Francisco Ballet Orchestra. Please see the full event description for information on special Family Performances.</summary_as_html>
    <badges>
      <badge>
        <name>hot_seller</name>
      </badge>
    </badges>
    <venue>
      <image>https://i.goldstar.com/gse_media/104/9/1401425warmemoutside.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.goldstar.com/venues/san-francisco-ca/war-memorial-opera-house</link>
      <address>
        <street_address>301 Van Ness Ave.</street_address>
        <extended_address/>
        <locality>San Francisco</locality>
        <region>CA</region>
        <postal_code>94102</postal_code>
        <country_name>United States</country_name>
      </address>
      <phone>415-865-2000</phone>
      <geocode_longitude>-122.419949</geocode_longitude>
      <name>War Memorial Opera House</name>
      <capacity>3148</capacity>
      <geocode_latitude>37.778281</geocode_latitude>
    </venue>
    <our_price_range>$49.00 - $56.00</our_price_range>
    <upcoming_dates>
      <event_date id="643061">
        <time_note>7:00pm (Family Performance)</time_note>
        <date>2012-12-13</date>
      </event_date>
    </upcoming_dates>
    <title_as_text>"Nutcracker"</title_as_text>
    <link>http://tracking.goldstar.com/aff_c?offer_id=6&amp;aff_id=1654&amp;aff_sub=63676</link>
    <title_as_html>&lt;em&gt;Nutcracker&lt;/em&gt;</title_as_html>
    <category_list>
      <category id="2">
        <name>Performing Arts</name>
      </category>
      <category id="8">
        <name>Family</name>
      </category>
    </category_list>
    <full_price_range>$98.00 - $112.00</full_price_range>
    <summary_as_text>On Christmas Eve 1944, "Nutcracker" made its American debut in San Francisco. So it's only fitting that when San Francisco Ballet Artistic Director and Principal Choreographer Helgi Tomasson set out to stage a new production of the beloved family favorite more than 60 years later, he chose the City by the Bay as the backdrop. Set in San Francisco during the 1915 World's Fair, Clara's dreamlike journey is an ode to the city's historical grandeur -- set amidst colorful, larger-than-life scenery, more than 200 dazzling costumed characters, and of course Tchaikovsky's beautiful score performed live by the world-class San Francisco Ballet Orchestra. Please see the full event description for information on special Family Performances.</summary_as_text>
    <deal_of_the_day/>
    <browsable_series>
      <series id="205">
        <name>Nutcracker 2012</name>
      </series>
      <series id="185">
        <name>Holiday Events 2012</name>
      </series>
    </browsable_series>
    <headline_as_html>San Francisco Ballet's &lt;em&gt;Nutcracker&lt;/em&gt;, Set in the City by the Bay</headline_as_html>
  </event>
</listings>
